<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.10.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-09-12T23:50:39+12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">Memoria : Hello World: This is a Blog and I’m Making a Post</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/09/10/second.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Memoria : Hello World: This is a Blog and I’m Making a Post" /><published>2024-09-10T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2024-09-10T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/09/10/second</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/09/10/second.html"><![CDATA[<p>I want to see how the page layout handles slightly longer titles.</p>

<p>I’ve been very busy (and exhausted) the past few weeks so I haven’t had time to get this thing going like I wanted. I still need to add tag pages, fill out the About Me information, and actually finish the layout. I want to sink my teeth into some gamedev stuff for fun once I’ve relaxed a little, so that’ll give me something to post about, I suppose. I will also be (at some point) setting up some proper hosting with a custom domain so that I’m not tied to this Github URL.</p>

<p>I’m also working on another page (linked at the top) where I collect mathematics notes and concepts, along with examples, explanation, etc… eventually. There’s not a lot there yet, and it’ll take a long time to fill out. I’m still getting the hang of Jekyll but it seems really fantastic and easy to use!</p>

<p>I was planning to blog about gaming here too; I’ve finished my latest playthough of Final Fantasy IX and I have a LOT to say about it, especially in regards to XIV and Dawntrail. I’ll write something once I get those thoughts together and collect some good reference screenshots.</p>]]></content><author><name>Cosmo</name></author><category term="dev" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to see how the page layout handles slightly longer titles.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Memoria : First!!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/08/21/first.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Memoria : First!!" /><published>2024-08-21T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2024-08-21T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/08/21/first</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/08/21/first.html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello world!</p>

<p>First test post! Things are up and running!</p>

<p>Fun fact: if you live in New Zealand and are working just after midnight, Github might think you are posting from the future and refuse to publish your correctly-dated entries. You may waste a lot of time trying to troubleshoot this. I am having a great day, thanks for asking.</p>

<p>At least it works now! I think!</p>]]></content><author><name>Cosmo</name></author><category term="dev" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello world!]]></summary></entry></feed>