<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.10.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-10-11T23:04:02+13:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">Memoria : Updates and Accidents</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/10/11/update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Memoria : Updates and Accidents" /><published>2024-10-11T00:00:00+13:00</published><updated>2024-10-11T00:00:00+13:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/10/11/update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/10/11/update.html"><![CDATA[<p>Whoops! Had a small Medical Scare the last few days. It’s fine. All my organs remain inside my body and in one piece. Probably.</p>

<p>This is one of the reasons work has been a bit slow, but I’m not really interested in making excuses. I am building up a lot of material that should get dumped on the math page in a few weeks. I’ll also finally have time to work on the layout. I have discovered CSS media queries and basically they have ruined my life by doing exactly the thing that I was struggling with. CSS is truly a neverending labyrinth of despair with no escape.</p>

<p>In other news, the rest of the year is good eating for JRPG enjoyers. <em>Metaphor: ReFantazio</em> is out, uh… today?!… and is currently getting overwhelmingly positive reviews. “<em>Persona</em> without the school setting” is something I’ve been craving for a long time, and while I was kind of planning to put this one in the backlog, I am finding myself buying into the hype just a little bit. Meanwhile, <em>Visions of Mana</em> has been out for a while and seems to have gone under the mainstream radar. It remains at the top of my backlog and I am very keen to start on it. The <em>Romancing SaGa 2</em> remake is coming later this month, followed by <em>Dragon Quest III</em> in November, and <em>Fantasian Neo Dimension</em> in December. Suffice to say my gaming schedule is fully packed for a good while. My biggest trial to come is not letting it all get in the way of my dev stuff. Thankfully I have at least one person besides myself holding me accountable, hah.</p>

<p>More math coming soon!!</p>]]></content><author><name>Cosmo</name></author><category term="dev" /><category term="gaming" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whoops! Had a small Medical Scare the last few days. It’s fine. All my organs remain inside my body and in one piece. Probably.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Memoria : New Time Waster Unlocked</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/09/23/plans.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Memoria : New Time Waster Unlocked" /><published>2024-09-23T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2024-09-23T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/09/23/plans</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/09/23/plans.html"><![CDATA[<p>I think I could probably spend the entire rest of my life fiddling around with CSS only to revert everything in the end anyway and have nothing to show for my efforts.</p>

<p>At this stage I have very little experience with Actual Practical Web Design that needs to be useable by humans, so one of the things on the agenda for the coming months is learning how to build things that are functional on mobile devices as well as desktop. You may notice the layout on my homepage currently doesn’t work on smaller screens at all. Please don’t look at my commit history. I will cry. I’m working on it.</p>

<p>I have also started learning Unity and C# on the side. I will definitely be sinking a lot more time into this and am very eager to do some game dev diary posts once I finish the tutorial projects I’m currently working on. I also miss Java! I have a growing list of small random projects I want to do. Maybe I’ll drop everything and do that instead! Who knows.</p>

<p>Anyway, the current site update roadmap is as follows:</p>

<ul>
  <li>
    <p>Daily updates to the math reference page; continuing to add basic definitions, concepts, etc. These will be expanded later with explanations, proofs, and examples.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p>Blog updates at least once a week. Hopefully this will help spur me to actually have things to write about.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p>Regular screwing around with layouts as I speedrun patching the holes in my web dev fundamentals.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p>Proper VPS hosting and custom domain(s) in ~3 months, if all goes to plan.</p>
  </li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Cosmo</name></author><category term="dev" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think I could probably spend the entire rest of my life fiddling around with CSS only to revert everything in the end anyway and have nothing to show for my efforts.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Memoria : Hello World: This is a Blog and I’m Making a Post</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/09/10/second.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Memoria : Hello World: This is a Blog and I’m Making a Post" /><published>2024-09-10T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2024-09-10T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/09/10/second</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/09/10/second.html"><![CDATA[<p>I want to see how the page layout handles slightly longer titles.</p>

<p>I’ve been very busy (and exhausted) the past few weeks so I haven’t had time to get this thing going like I wanted. I still need to add tag pages, fill out the About Me information, and actually finish the layout. I want to sink my teeth into some gamedev stuff for fun once I’ve relaxed a little, so that’ll give me something to post about, I suppose. I will also be (at some point) setting up some proper hosting with a custom domain so that I’m not tied to this Github URL.</p>

<p>I’m also working on another page (linked at the top) where I collect mathematics notes and concepts, along with examples, explanation, etc… eventually. There’s not a lot there yet, and it’ll take a long time to fill out. I’m still getting the hang of Jekyll but it seems really fantastic and easy to use!</p>

<p>I was planning to blog about gaming here too; I’ve finished my latest playthough of Final Fantasy IX and I have a LOT to say about it, especially in regards to XIV and Dawntrail. I’ll write something once I get those thoughts together and collect some good reference screenshots.</p>]]></content><author><name>Cosmo</name></author><category term="dev" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to see how the page layout handles slightly longer titles.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Memoria : First!!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/08/21/first.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Memoria : First!!" /><published>2024-08-21T00:00:00+12:00</published><updated>2024-08-21T00:00:00+12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/08/21/first</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/08/21/first.html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello world!</p>

<p>First test post! Things are up and running!</p>

<p>Fun fact: if you live in New Zealand and are working just after midnight, Github might think you are posting from the future and refuse to publish your correctly-dated entries. You may waste a lot of time trying to troubleshoot this. I am having a great day, thanks for asking.</p>

<p>At least it works now! I think!</p>]]></content><author><name>Cosmo</name></author><category term="dev" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello world!]]></summary></entry></feed>